respond.com 2001-08-13

# Respond.com | Privacy Policy

Overview   
[](https://www.truste.org/validate/3446)Respond.com knows how important your privacy is to you, and we appreciate you trusting us to handle your personal information responsibly and with integrity. The information we gather is used to provide you with a good experience and to help us improve our service for you. This document describes Respond.com's privacy policy and practices. **Please note that you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy by visiting and using Respond.com.**

Our Commitment   
Respond.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our buyers and businesses. Since we collect certain types of information at the time our service is used, we have created this document to let our users know what information we collect, how the collected information is used to benefit our users, and how we protect the information that is provided to us. Rest assured, the privacy of our buyers and businesses is of utmost importance to us, and Respond.com will make every effort to ensure that our users are effectively informed and protected. 

Buyer Protection   
In order to submit a request to our community of businesses, buyers are required to provide us with an email address, as our service is email-based. The email address allows us to deliver business responses to the buyer through email. Buyers' email addresses are never disclosed to third parties without consent. In certain categories, we may require a ZIP Code to process a request for the purpose of geographically matching buyers with businesses. In some cases, businesses don't use email and may need another means of contact, such as a phone or fax number. In such cases, we will ask for this additional information, and businesses may then contact the buyer directly. Note: Businesses may not contact the buyer for any reason other than to address the information or assistance specifically requested in the buyer request and may not contact the buyer beyond the timeframe that the request is open. 

Respond.com also offers buyers the opportunity to request news, special offer information, and/or information about promotions. These opportunities are completely optional, and buyers are not obligated to take advantage of them. Respond.com will always ask before sending any information or promotional offering. 

Respond.com reserves the right to provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Web site information to reputable third party vendors, but these statistics will not include any personal or identifying information. Respond.com reserves the right to post on its Web site the text in the "Details" box and additional product or service information inputted by buyers in the request form. However, we will not post any information included in a buyer request that includes any personally identifiable information. Buyers have the option to cancel requests at any time. 

Business Protection   
To become a registered business with Respond.com, interested parties must provide us with contact information. Contact information submitted for account administration purposes is considered strictly confidential, will not be shared with buyers without consent, and will be used for billing purposes and to provide updates about the Respond.com service. Contact information submitted for the Business Profile is intended for buyer viewing and will be shared with buyers as appropriate. Businesses may update or revise any account and contact information by visiting the "Manage Account" and "Billing Information" sections of our Web site. Businesses may deactivate their account by contacting Customer Support at [support@respond.com](mailto:support@respond.com). 

Contact information will be included in the Response emails Respond.com sends on behalf of businesses. This information is necessary for buyers to contact businesses directly. Businesses select how they wish to be contacted and may opt to be contacted in any or all of the following ways: phone, fax, email, pager, or the business's Web site. 

We use cookies to enhance the Respond.com experience   
Cookies are small amounts of data delivered to a user's hard drive by a Web browser. The use of cookies enables Respond.com to process requests quickly, thereby enhancing the Respond.com experience for both buyers and businesses. Cookies are not required, but they are recommended. Businesses are especially encouraged to leave cookies on, as it becomes difficult to use the system without them. 

Information we collect   
Certain information is automatically tracked about our users when they use our Web site. This information includes the URL that the user just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), the URL that the user goes to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), the operating system the user is using, the browser the user is using, and the user's IP address. This information is collected to analyze trends, track user movement and use, gather broad demographic information, and administer the site. Many sites automatically collect this information. 

Note   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Except where noted, information is only for our registration and accounting purposes. Please note that if our services are accessed through one of our partner sites, we may share the information submitted through the partner's site with that specific partner, and we do not have control over and are not responsible for the privacy policies of our partners. 

We ask for your consent to our Privacy Policy   
By using Respond.com you agree to the above uses of your personal information. If at any time this policy changes, those changes will be posted to this page so that you are aware of our intent to better protect your privacy. You will be notified through email prior to any substantive changes in how we use your personal information. At that time, we will notify businesses as to how they may cancel their service (if they wish), and we will notify buyers as to how they may opt-out of receiving marketing communications (if they wish). We have obtained consent from all of the businesses who have provided us with the testimonials we occasionally post on our Web site. 

We ask for your comments and questions   
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact Customer Support at [support@respond.com](mailto:support@respond.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). 

TRUSTe Privacy Program   
Respond.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit initiative whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the principles of disclosure and informed consent. When you visit a Web site displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, you can expect to be notified of: what personally identifiable information of yours is collected; what organization is collecting the information; how the information is used; with whom the information may be shared; what choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information; what kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under the company's control; and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

BBB _OnLine_ ® Privacy Program   
[](http://www.bbbonline.org/cnfm2.cfm?company=07221999014626)Respond.com is also a participant in the BBB _OnLine_ ® Privacy Program. The BBB _OnLine_ Privacy Program is backed by an organization noted for its expertise and experience in conducting successful national self-regulation programs—the Council of Better Business Bureaus. The mission of BBB _OnLine_ is to promote trust and confidence on the Internet by advocating ethical online business practices. Further information about this program and the BBB _OnLine_ Privacy standards is available at [http://www.bbbonline.org](http://www.bbbonline.org/). 

The Respond.com Privacy Policy was last updated on 4/5/01
